{"What kind of file has the extension .dbf ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "file", "has", "the", "extension", ".dbf", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In what Olympic Games did Nadia Comaneci become popular ?": [["In", "what", "Olympic", "Games", "did", "Nadia", "Comaneci", "become", "popular", "?"], [["Nadia", "PERSON"], ["Comaneci", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "In"]], "What 's the only mammal that can 't jump ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "only", "mammal", "that", "can", "'t", "jump", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Which comic book was not spawned directly from the pulp magazines ?": [["Which", "comic", "book", "was", "not", "spawned", "directly", "from", "the", "pulp", "magazines", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "How long does cocaine stay in your system ?": [["How", "long", "does", "cocaine", "stay", "in", "your", "system", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What color is indigo ?": [["What", "color", "is", "indigo", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the singular of dice ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "singular", "of", "dice", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the term for any four-sided figure ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "term", "for", "any", "four-sided", "figure", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In what year did Ireland elect its first woman president ?": [["In", "what", "year", "did", "Ireland", "elect", "its", "first", "woman", "president", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["Ireland", "LOCATION"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "What do camels store in their humps ?": [["What", "do", "camels", "store", "in", "their", "humps", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What line of luggage is named after a famous American flier ?": [["What", "line", "of", "luggage", "is", "named", "after", "a", "famous", "American", "flier", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many oceans are there and name them ?": [["How", "many", "oceans", "are", "there", "and", "name", "them", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What year did the NFL go on strike ?": [["What", "year", "did", "the", "NFL", "go", "on", "strike", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["NFL", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How wide is the Atlantic Ocean ?": [["How", "wide", "is", "the", "Atlantic", "Ocean", "?"], [["Ocean", "LOCATION"], ["Atlantic", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What device provided a new way to listen to music in 1963 ?": [["What", "device", "provided", "a", "new", "way", "to", "listen", "to", "music", "in", "1963", "?"], [["1963", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How old was the youngest president of the United States ?": [["How", "old", "was", "the", "youngest", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], [["United", "LOCATION"], ["States", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What Italian liner was hijacked in 1985 ?": [["What", "Italian", "liner", "was", "hijacked", "in", "1985", "?"], [["1985", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What Jules Verne novel features scientists held captive in the submarine Nautilus ?": [["What", "Jules", "Verne", "novel", "features", "scientists", "held", "captive", "in", "the", "submarine", "Nautilus", "?"], [["Verne", "PERSON"], ["Jules", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What year did the Vietnam War end ?": [["What", "year", "did", "the", "Vietnam", "War", "end", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many holes are there in a tenpin bowling ball ?": [["How", "many", "holes", "are", "there", "in", "a", "tenpin", "bowling", "ball", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What color are a cherry tree 's flowers ?": [["What", "color", "are", "a", "cherry", "tree", "'s", "flowers", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the American dollar equivalent for 8 pounds in the U.K. ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "American", "dollar", "equivalent", "for", "8", "pounds", "in", "the", "U.K.", "?"], [["pounds", "MONEY"], ["8", "MONEY"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the speed of light ?": [["What", "is", "the", "speed", "of", "light", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What rum is so `` mixable '' it is a one-brand bar ?": [["What", "rum", "is", "so", "``", "mixable", "''", "it", "is", "a", "one-brand", "bar", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the conversion rate between dollars and pounds ?": [["What", "is", "the", "conversion", "rate", "between", "dollars", "and", "pounds", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is money made of ?": [["What", "is", "money", "made", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the mean income of the top 10 % , top 5 % , and top 1 % ?": [["What", "is", "the", "mean", "income", "of", "the", "top", "10", "%", ",", "top", "5", "%", ",", "and", "top", "1", "%", "?"], [["5", "PERCENT"], ["10", "PERCENT"], ["%", "PERCENT"], ["1", "PERCENT"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What beer is ` rockin ' America ? ''": [["What", "beer", "is", "`", "rockin", "'", "America", "?", "''"], [["America", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Which airplane did Fawaz Younis hijack ?": [["Which", "airplane", "did", "Fawaz", "Younis", "hijack", "?"], [["Younis", "PERSON"], ["Fawaz", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "Name one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World .": [["Name", "one", "of", "the", "Seven", "Wonders", "of", "the", "Ancient", "World", "."], [["one", "NUMBER"], ["Seven", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "What was the first ready-to-eat breakfast cereal ?": [["What", "was", "the", "first", "ready-to-eat", "breakfast", "cereal", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of going to bed ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "going", "to", "bed", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What war was fought by the Spanish as far as the Philippines ?": [["What", "war", "was", "fought", "by", "the", "Spanish", "as", "far", "as", "the", "Philippines", "?"], [["Philippines", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What war saw a naval battle between the luxury liners Cap Trafalgar and the Carmania ?": [["What", "war", "saw", "a", "naval", "battle", "between", "the", "luxury", "liners", "Cap", "Trafalgar", "and", "the", "Carmania", "?"], [["Trafalgar", "PERSON"], ["Cap", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the best way to travel in Japan ?": [["What", "is", "the", "best", "way", "to", "travel", "in", "Japan", "?"], [["Japan", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of the 1899 policy forced on China by which all nations had equal trading rights ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "the", "1899", "policy", "forced", "on", "China", "by", "which", "all", "nations", "had", "equal", "trading", "rights", "?"], [["1899", "DATE"], ["China", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Dr. Seuss ' most popular book ?": [["What", "is", "Dr.", "Seuss", "'", "most", "popular", "book", "?"], [["Seuss", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many penny-farthings are there on a Trivial Pursuit game board ?": [["How", "many", "penny-farthings", "are", "there", "on", "a", "Trivial", "Pursuit", "game", "board", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What do chefs call The Master Spice ?": [["What", "do", "chefs", "call", "The", "Master", "Spice", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "For what disease is the drug Sinemet used as a treatment ?": [["For", "what", "disease", "is", "the", "drug", "Sinemet", "used", "as", "a", "treatment", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "For"]], "How many years do fossils take to form ?": [["How", "many", "years", "do", "fossils", "take", "to", "form", "?"], [["years", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the Islamic equivalent of the Red Cross ?": [["What", "is", "the", "Islamic", "equivalent", "of", "the", "Red", "Cross", "?"], [["Cross", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Red", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of stings ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "stings", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many inches tall is Stuart Little at birth ?": [["How", "many", "inches", "tall", "is", "Stuart", "Little", "at", "birth", "?"], [["Little", "PERSON"], ["Stuart", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many Canadians emmigrate each year ?": [["How", "many", "Canadians", "emmigrate", "each", "year", "?"], [["year", "SET"], ["each", "SET"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What are the names of the different toes ?": [["What", "are", "the", "names", "of", "the", "different", "toes", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What day is August 13 , 1971 ?": [["What", "day", "is", "August", "13", ",", "1971", "?"], [["13", "DATE"], ["day", "DURATION"], ["August", "DATE"], ["1971", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "When did the vesuvius last erupt ?": [["When", "did", "the", "vesuvius", "last", "erupt", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What 's the term for a bet before cards are dealt ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "term", "for", "a", "bet", "before", "cards", "are", "dealt", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What TV station did Mary Richards work for ?": [["What", "TV", "station", "did", "Mary", "Richards", "work", "for", "?"], [["Richards", "PERSON"], ["Mary", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What Hollywood dog died in the arms of Jean Harlow in 1932 ?": [["What", "Hollywood", "dog", "died", "in", "the", "arms", "of", "Jean", "Harlow", "in", "1932", "?"], [["Hollywood", "LOCATION"], ["1932", "DATE"], ["Harlow", "PERSON"], ["Jean", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "The operating system that runs on IBM-compatible machines is called what ?": [["The", "operating", "system", "that", "runs", "on", "IBM-compatible", "machines", "is", "called", "what", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "The"]], "How many feet in a mile ?": [["How", "many", "feet", "in", "a", "mile", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many lawyers are there in the state of New Jersey ?": [["How", "many", "lawyers", "are", "there", "in", "the", "state", "of", "New", "Jersey", "?"], [["New", "LOCATION"], ["Jersey", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "When was CNN 's first broadcast ?": [["When", "was", "CNN", "'s", "first", "broadcast", "?"], [["CNN", "ORGANIZATION"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What product 's ads claim that it `` eliminates odors , kills household germs , mold , and mildew '' ?": [["What", "product", "'s", "ads", "claim", "that", "it", "``", "eliminates", "odors", ",", "kills", "household", "germs", ",", "mold", ",", "and", "mildew", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was the first practical commercial typewriter marketed ?": [["When", "was", "the", "first", "practical", "commercial", "typewriter", "marketed", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is the recipe or formula for Coca-Cola ?": [["What", "is", "the", "recipe", "or", "formula", "for", "Coca-Cola", "?"], [["Coca-Cola", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the name of the kids ' show from Canadian Public TV with the singing pineapple ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "kids", "'", "show", "from", "Canadian", "Public", "TV", "with", "the", "singing", "pineapple", "?"], [["TV", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Canadian", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Public", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the education system in the 1960 's ?": [["What", "was", "the", "education", "system", "in", "the", "1960", "'s", "?"], [["1960", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the four most widely-used languages in North America ?": [["What", "are", "the", "four", "most", "widely-used", "languages", "in", "North", "America", "?"], [["North", "LOCATION"], ["America", "LOCATION"], ["four", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the most famous German word in the English language ?": [["What", "is", "the", "most", "famous", "German", "word", "in", "the", "English", "language", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the zodiac sign for August 14 ?": [["What", "is", "the", "zodiac", "sign", "for", "August", "14", "?"], [["August", "DATE"], ["14", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What card game has variations called Canfield , Klondike and Spider ?": [["What", "card", "game", "has", "variations", "called", "Canfield", ",", "Klondike", "and", "Spider", "?"], [["Canfield", "PERSON"], ["Klondike", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many e-commerce companies are started every day ?": [["How", "many", "e-commerce", "companies", "are", "started", "every", "day", "?"], [["every", "SET"], ["day", "SET"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the average date when most malls begin putting up Christmas holiday decorations ?": [["What", "is", "the", "average", "date", "when", "most", "malls", "begin", "putting", "up", "Christmas", "holiday", "decorations", "?"], [["Christmas", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "Which Beatles disc cover honors the Rolling Stones ?": [["Which", "Beatles", "disc", "cover", "honors", "the", "Rolling", "Stones", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "What 's the name of Jacques Cousteau 's research ship ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "name", "of", "Jacques", "Cousteau", "'s", "research", "ship", "?"], [["Jacques", "PERSON"], ["Cousteau", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What new games are available for Nintendo 64 ?": [["What", "new", "games", "are", "available", "for", "Nintendo", "64", "?"], [["Nintendo", "ORGANIZATION"], ["64", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many hours of work does it take a typist to complete a 100-page screenplay ?": [["How", "many", "hours", "of", "work", "does", "it", "take", "a", "typist", "to", "complete", "a", "100-page", "screenplay", "?"], [["hours", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is a ball that hits the foul pole called ?": [["What", "is", "a", "ball", "that", "hits", "the", "foul", "pole", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of sinning ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "sinning", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Susan B. Anthony 's birthday ?": [["What", "is", "Susan", "B.", "Anthony", "'s", "birthday", "?"], [["B", "PERSON"], ["Susan", "PERSON"], ["Anthony", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "To get the most caffeine , what soda should I drink ?": [["To", "get", "the", "most", "caffeine", ",", "what", "soda", "should", "I", "drink", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "To"]], "How many people on the ground were killed from the bombing of Pan Am Flight 103 over Lockerbie , Scotland , December 21 ?": [["How", "many", "people", "on", "the", "ground", "were", "killed", "from", "the", "bombing", "of", "Pan", "Am", "Flight", "103", "over", "Lockerbie", ",", "Scotland", ",", "December", "21", "?"], [["Am", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Scotland", "LOCATION"], ["Lockerbie", "LOCATION"], ["Pan", "ORGANIZATION"], ["December", "DATE"], ["21", "DATE"], ["103", "NUMBER"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What new year is celebrated on February 16th ?": [["What", "new", "year", "is", "celebrated", "on", "February", "16th", "?"], [["year", "DATE"], ["16th", "DATE"], ["February", "DATE"], ["new", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What eating utensils are used for handicapped kids ?": [["What", "eating", "utensils", "are", "used", "for", "handicapped", "kids", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What war did Johnny Reb and Billy Yank fight ?": [["What", "war", "did", "Johnny", "Reb", "and", "Billy", "Yank", "fight", "?"], [["Yank", "PERSON"], ["Johnny", "PERSON"], ["Billy", "PERSON"], ["Reb", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the smallest bird in Britain ?": [["What", "is", "the", "smallest", "bird", "in", "Britain", "?"], [["Britain", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What nutrients are for healthy bones and teeth ?": [["What", "nutrients", "are", "for", "healthy", "bones", "and", "teeth", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When did the Berlin Wall go up ?": [["When", "did", "the", "Berlin", "Wall", "go", "up", "?"], [["Wall", "LOCATION"], ["Berlin", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is a fear of being cold ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "being", "cold", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What kind of gas is in a fluorescent bulb ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "gas", "is", "in", "a", "fluorescent", "bulb", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What year was the NAACP founded ?": [["What", "year", "was", "the", "NAACP", "founded", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["NAACP", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "When do you plant winter wheat ?": [["When", "do", "you", "plant", "winter", "wheat", "?"], [["winter", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What color of Monopoly properties are landed on most often ?": [["What", "color", "of", "Monopoly", "properties", "are", "landed", "on", "most", "often", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many tiles did the Space Shuttle Columbia lose on its second flight ?": [["How", "many", "tiles", "did", "the", "Space", "Shuttle", "Columbia", "lose", "on", "its", "second", "flight", "?"], [["second", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How tall is kilamanjaro ?": [["How", "tall", "is", "kilamanjaro", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is `` the soft drink for adults '' ?": [["What", "is", "``", "the", "soft", "drink", "for", "adults", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the second-most-used vowel in English ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "second-most-used", "vowel", "in", "English", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much do drugs to treat tuberculosis cost ?": [["How", "much", "do", "drugs", "to", "treat", "tuberculosis", "cost", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How old do you have to be in order to rent a car in Italy ?": [["How", "old", "do", "you", "have", "to", "be", "in", "order", "to", "rent", "a", "car", "in", "Italy", "?"], [["Italy", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What year did Hitler die ?": [["What", "year", "did", "Hitler", "die", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["Hitler", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is a fear of children ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "children", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In which year was New Zealand excluded from the ANZUS alliance ?": [["In", "which", "year", "was", "New", "Zealand", "excluded", "from", "the", "ANZUS", "alliance", "?"], [["ANZUS", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Zealand", "LOCATION"], ["year", "DURATION"], ["New", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "On which date is the Ukrainians ' Christmas ?": [["On", "which", "date", "is", "the", "Ukrainians", "'", "Christmas", "?"], [["Christmas", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "On"]], "What 's a male witch called ?": [["What", "'s", "a", "male", "witch", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What term does a Czech use to describe a Pole ?": [["What", "term", "does", "a", "Czech", "use", "to", "describe", "a", "Pole", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does a barometer measure ?": [["What", "does", "a", "barometer", "measure", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was Hurricane Hugo ?": [["When", "was", "Hurricane", "Hugo", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "When did Lucelly Garcia , a former ambassador of Columbia to Honduras , die ?": [["When", "did", "Lucelly", "Garcia", ",", "a", "former", "ambassador", "of", "Columbia", "to", "Honduras", ",", "die", "?"], [["Columbia", "LOCATION"], ["Honduras", "LOCATION"], ["Garcia", "PERSON"], ["Lucelly", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "Which mammal lives , breeds , eats , and sleeps underground ?": [["Which", "mammal", "lives", ",", "breeds", ",", "eats", ",", "and", "sleeps", "underground", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "How much of an apple is water ?": [["How", "much", "of", "an", "apple", "is", "water", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What 's men 's par on a 455-yard golf hole ?": [["What", "'s", "men", "'s", "par", "on", "a", "455-yard", "golf", "hole", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the heaviest naturally occurring element ?": [["What", "is", "the", "heaviest", "naturally", "occurring", "element", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When are sheep shorn ?": [["When", "are", "sheep", "shorn", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What were the ceremony traditions like during the Elizabethian times ?": [["What", "were", "the", "ceremony", "traditions", "like", "during", "the", "Elizabethian", "times", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are emblazoned on the Jolly Roger ?": [["What", "are", "emblazoned", "on", "the", "Jolly", "Roger", "?"], [["Roger", "PERSON"], ["Jolly", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What amount of folic acid should an expectant mother take daily ?": [["What", "amount", "of", "folic", "acid", "should", "an", "expectant", "mother", "take", "daily", "?"], [["daily", "SET"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How far is the service line from the net in tennis ?": [["How", "far", "is", "the", "service", "line", "from", "the", "net", "in", "tennis", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is Shirley MacLaine known as ?": [["What", "is", "Shirley", "MacLaine", "known", "as", "?"], [["Shirley", "PERSON"], ["MacLaine", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much electricity does the brain need to work ?": [["How", "much", "electricity", "does", "the", "brain", "need", "to", "work", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What brand of white rum is still made in Cuba ?": [["What", "brand", "of", "white", "rum", "is", "still", "made", "in", "Cuba", "?"], [["Cuba", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Which mayonnaise refers to itself as `` real '' mayonnaise ?": [["Which", "mayonnaise", "refers", "to", "itself", "as", "``", "real", "''", "mayonnaise", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "What films featured the character Popeye Doyle ?": [["What", "films", "featured", "the", "character", "Popeye", "Doyle", "?"], [["Popeye", "PERSON"], ["Doyle", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was the first stained glass window made ?": [["When", "was", "the", "first", "stained", "glass", "window", "made", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What animal has the biggest eyes ?": [["What", "animal", "has", "the", "biggest", "eyes", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What year did Oklahoma become a state ?": [["What", "year", "did", "Oklahoma", "become", "a", "state", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["Oklahoma", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many types of cheese are there in France ?": [["How", "many", "types", "of", "cheese", "are", "there", "in", "France", "?"], [["France", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What currency do they use in Brazil ?": [["What", "currency", "do", "they", "use", "in", "Brazil", "?"], [["Brazil", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What album put The Beatles on the cover of Time in 1967 ?": [["What", "album", "put", "The", "Beatles", "on", "the", "cover", "of", "Time", "in", "1967", "?"], [["Time", "ORGANIZATION"], ["1967", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What kind of substance is dextropropoxyphen napsylate ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "substance", "is", "dextropropoxyphen", "napsylate", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 1966 boob tube bomb took astronauts back to prehistoric times ?": [["What", "1966", "boob", "tube", "bomb", "took", "astronauts", "back", "to", "prehistoric", "times", "?"], [["1966", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many warmup pitches does a reliever get coming into a baseball game ?": [["How", "many", "warmup", "pitches", "does", "a", "reliever", "get", "coming", "into", "a", "baseball", "game", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the only animal that can turn its stomach inside out ?": [["What", "is", "the", "only", "animal", "that", "can", "turn", "its", "stomach", "inside", "out", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When were fish first believed to be found on earth ?": [["When", "were", "fish", "first", "believed", "to", "be", "found", "on", "earth", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is the most efficient way to start a barbeque ?": [["What", "is", "the", "most", "efficient", "way", "to", "start", "a", "barbeque", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Madonna hocks which soft drink ?": [["Madonna", "hocks", "which", "soft", "drink", "?"], [["Madonna", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Madonna"]], "How much did Varian Associates try to sell its vacuum products division to the BOC group for ?": [["How", "much", "did", "Varian", "Associates", "try", "to", "sell", "its", "vacuum", "products", "division", "to", "the", "BOC", "group", "for", "?"], [["Varian", "ORGANIZATION"], ["BOC", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Associates", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the medical term for cancer of the blood ?": [["What", "is", "the", "medical", "term", "for", "cancer", "of", "the", "blood", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When will Jean Aeul publish her next book ?": [["When", "will", "Jean", "Aeul", "publish", "her", "next", "book", "?"], [["Aeul", "PERSON"], ["Jean", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How fast is the speed of light ?": [["How", "fast", "is", "the", "speed", "of", "light", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What four-legged creature did a Cornell University study say would make man 's best companion in space ?": [["What", "four-legged", "creature", "did", "a", "Cornell", "University", "study", "say", "would", "make", "man", "'s", "best", "companion", "in", "space", "?"], [["Cornell", "ORGANIZATION"], ["University", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the rarest coin ?": [["What", "is", "the", "rarest", "coin", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How long did Shea and Gould practice law in Los Angeles ?": [["How", "long", "did", "Shea", "and", "Gould", "practice", "law", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "?"], [["Angeles", "LOCATION"], ["Gould", "PERSON"], ["Shea", "PERSON"], ["Los", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many lakes are there on the Earth ?": [["How", "many", "lakes", "are", "there", "on", "the", "Earth", "?"], [["Earth", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What do West Indian steel bands use as instruments ?": [["What", "do", "West", "Indian", "steel", "bands", "use", "as", "instruments", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many liters in a gallon ?": [["How", "many", "liters", "in", "a", "gallon", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What star-faring race brought about the Inhumans on Marvel 's Earth ?": [["What", "star-faring", "race", "brought", "about", "the", "Inhumans", "on", "Marvel", "'s", "Earth", "?"], [["Earth", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What food can I use to catch a possum ?": [["What", "food", "can", "I", "use", "to", "catch", "a", "possum", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the distinguishing mark on the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?": [["What", "was", "the", "distinguishing", "mark", "on", "the", "``", "Little", "Rascals", "''", "dog", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the current population for these countries : France , Spain , Italy , Greece , Austria , Germany , Switzerland , the Netherlands ?": [["What", "is", "the", "current", "population", "for", "these", "countries", ":", "France", ",", "Spain", ",", "Italy", ",", "Greece", ",", "Austria", ",", "Germany", ",", "Switzerland", ",", "the", "Netherlands", "?"], [["Austria", "LOCATION"], ["Switzerland", "LOCATION"], ["current", "DATE"], ["Netherlands", "LOCATION"], ["Germany", "LOCATION"], ["Italy", "LOCATION"], ["France", "LOCATION"], ["Spain", "LOCATION"], ["Greece", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is a female rabbit called ?": [["What", "is", "a", "female", "rabbit", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the gestation period for a cat ?": [["What", "is", "the", "gestation", "period", "for", "a", "cat", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What do you call a newborn kangaroo ?": [["What", "do", "you", "call", "a", "newborn", "kangaroo", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many Israeli athletes were killed at the Munich Olympics ?": [["How", "many", "Israeli", "athletes", "were", "killed", "at", "the", "Munich", "Olympics", "?"], [["Munich", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What civil war was fought between 1936 and 1939 ?": [["What", "civil", "war", "was", "fought", "between", "1936", "and", "1939", "?"], [["1939", "DATE"], ["1936", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of the Protestant revolt against the supremacy of the Pope ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "the", "Protestant", "revolt", "against", "the", "supremacy", "of", "the", "Pope", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was Franklin Roosevelt 's program for economic recovery called during the Great Depression ?": [["What", "was", "Franklin", "Roosevelt", "'s", "program", "for", "economic", "recovery", "called", "during", "the", "Great", "Depression", "?"], [["Franklin", "PERSON"], ["Roosevelt", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What year was Mozart born ?": [["What", "year", "was", "Mozart", "born", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["Mozart", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What beer advertised that it had `` three rings '' ?": [["What", "beer", "advertised", "that", "it", "had", "``", "three", "rings", "''", "?"], [["three", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How big is the largest diamond ?": [["How", "big", "is", "the", "largest", "diamond", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What primary colors do you mix to make orange ?": [["What", "primary", "colors", "do", "you", "mix", "to", "make", "orange", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When did CNN begin broadcasting ?": [["When", "did", "CNN", "begin", "broadcasting", "?"], [["CNN", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How many countries watch MTV Europe ?": [["How", "many", "countries", "watch", "MTV", "Europe", "?"], [["Europe", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What impenetrable system of French fortifications was built along the German frontier before World War II ?": [["What", "impenetrable", "system", "of", "French", "fortifications", "was", "built", "along", "the", "German", "frontier", "before", "World", "War", "II", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the name of the Michelangelo painting that shows two hands with fingers touching ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "Michelangelo", "painting", "that", "shows", "two", "hands", "with", "fingers", "touching", "?"], [["Michelangelo", "PERSON"], ["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What TV show did John Sebastian sing the theme for ?": [["What", "TV", "show", "did", "John", "Sebastian", "sing", "the", "theme", "for", "?"], [["Sebastian", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many athletes did Puerto Rico enter in the 1984 Winter Olympics ?": [["How", "many", "athletes", "did", "Puerto", "Rico", "enter", "in", "the", "1984", "Winter", "Olympics", "?"], [["1984", "DATE"], ["Rico", "LOCATION"], ["Winter", "DATE"], ["the", "DATE"], ["Puerto", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "When was the Triangle Shirtwaist fire ?": [["When", "was", "the", "Triangle", "Shirtwaist", "fire", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "How much money can a person be fined for having a dog on a beach ?": [["How", "much", "money", "can", "a", "person", "be", "fined", "for", "having", "a", "dog", "on", "a", "beach", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many endangered species are there in the world ?": [["How", "many", "endangered", "species", "are", "there", "in", "the", "world", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What does an edentulous smile lack ?": [["What", "does", "an", "edentulous", "smile", "lack", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many grooves are on a dime 's edge ?": [["How", "many", "grooves", "are", "on", "a", "dime", "'s", "edge", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is a camel hair brush actually made out of ?": [["What", "is", "a", "camel", "hair", "brush", "actually", "made", "out", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What gasses are in the troposphere ?": [["What", "gasses", "are", "in", "the", "troposphere", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many wives did Brigham Young have ?": [["How", "many", "wives", "did", "Brigham", "Young", "have", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What two colors are you blind to if you suffer from protanopia ?": [["What", "two", "colors", "are", "you", "blind", "to", "if", "you", "suffer", "from", "protanopia", "?"], [["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many frames does a disk camera shoot ?": [["How", "many", "frames", "does", "a", "disk", "camera", "shoot", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "By how much will the California state gas tax rise by the year 2000 ?": [["By", "how", "much", "will", "the", "California", "state", "gas", "tax", "rise", "by", "the", "year", "2000", "?"], [["year", "DATE"], ["California", "LOCATION"], ["the", "DATE"], ["2000", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "By"]], "What 's the maximum number of clubs a golfer may use in a round ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "maximum", "number", "of", "clubs", "a", "golfer", "may", "use", "in", "a", "round", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "When did the Chernobyl nuclear accident occur ?": [["When", "did", "the", "Chernobyl", "nuclear", "accident", "occur", "?"], [["Chernobyl", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "In which Tennessee Williams play is one of the characters killed and devoured by a mob of starving children ?": [["In", "which", "Tennessee", "Williams", "play", "is", "one", "of", "the", "characters", "killed", "and", "devoured", "by", "a", "mob", "of", "starving", "children", "?"], [["one", "NUMBER"], ["Williams", "PERSON"], ["Tennessee", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "In"]], "What is the longest word in the English language ?": [["What", "is", "the", "longest", "word", "in", "the", "English", "language", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many stars are there in Big Dipper ?": [["How", "many", "stars", "are", "there", "in", "Big", "Dipper", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many letters appear with the numbers 2 to 9 on a telephone dial ?": [["How", "many", "letters", "appear", "with", "the", "numbers", "2", "to", "9", "on", "a", "telephone", "dial", "?"], [["9", "NUMBER"], ["2", "NUMBER"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many pairs of legs does a lobster have ?": [["How", "many", "pairs", "of", "legs", "does", "a", "lobster", "have", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What creature is the absolute fastest in moving in the world , birds , mammals , etc . , ?": [["What", "creature", "is", "the", "absolute", "fastest", "in", "moving", "in", "the", "world", ",", "birds", ",", "mammals", ",", "etc", ".", ",", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What kind of crystals exist ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "crystals", "exist", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Where is the human skin least sensitive ?": [["Where", "is", "the", "human", "skin", "least", "sensitive", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Where"]], "What did 8 , CD NNS VBP TO VB NNP POS NN .": [["What", "did", "8", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], [["8", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What TV series features the adventures of a married couple named Jonathan and Jennifer ?": [["What", "TV", "series", "features", "the", "adventures", "of", "a", "married", "couple", "named", "Jonathan", "and", "Jennifer", "?"], [["Jennifer", "PERSON"], ["Jonathan", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are different products of petroleum ?": [["What", "are", "different", "products", "of", "petroleum", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When do MORMONS believe Christ was born ?": [["When", "do", "MORMONS", "believe", "Christ", "was", "born", "?"], [["Christ", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What are the two largest birds on earth ?": [["What", "are", "the", "two", "largest", "birds", "on", "earth", "?"], [["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In 1990 , what day of the week did Christmas fall on ?": [["In", "1990", ",", "what", "day", "of", "the", "week", "did", "Christmas", "fall", "on", "?"], [["Christmas", "DATE"], ["fall", "DATE"], ["of", "DATE"], ["week", "DATE"], ["day", "DATE"], ["the", "DATE"], ["1990", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "What is a fear of rejection ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "rejection", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When were William Shakespeare 's twins born ?": [["When", "were", "William", "Shakespeare", "'s", "twins", "born", "?"], [["Shakespeare", "PERSON"], ["William", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What was the death toll at the eruption of Mount Pinatubo ?": [["What", "was", "the", "death", "toll", "at", "the", "eruption", "of", "Mount", "Pinatubo", "?"], [["Pinatubo", "LOCATION"], ["Mount", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What sport features snatches and clean jerks ?": [["What", "sport", "features", "snatches", "and", "clean", "jerks", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many Russians have landed on the moon ?": [["How", "many", "Russians", "have", "landed", "on", "the", "moon", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What Hermann Hesse book gave its name to a rock group ?": [["What", "Hermann", "Hesse", "book", "gave", "its", "name", "to", "a", "rock", "group", "?"], [["Hesse", "PERSON"], ["Hermann", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What five cards make up a perfect Cribbage hand ?": [["What", "five", "cards", "make", "up", "a", "perfect", "Cribbage", "hand", "?"], [["five", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What future movie treat was introduced to American colonists in 1603 by Native Americans ?": [["What", "future", "movie", "treat", "was", "introduced", "to", "American", "colonists", "in", "1603", "by", "Native", "Americans", "?"], [["1603", "DATE"], ["future", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How often are brain cells replaced ?": [["How", "often", "are", "brain", "cells", "replaced", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What 's the dumbest domesticated animal ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "dumbest", "domesticated", "animal", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of Betty Boop 's dog ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "Betty", "Boop", "'s", "dog", "?"], [["Betty", "PERSON"], ["Boop", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What comic strip sometimes features a mailman named Beasley ?": [["What", "comic", "strip", "sometimes", "features", "a", "mailman", "named", "Beasley", "?"], [["Beasley", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What were Baffin , Frobisher and Franklin looking for ?": [["What", "were", "Baffin", ",", "Frobisher", "and", "Franklin", "looking", "for", "?"], [["Frobisher", "PERSON"], ["Franklin", "PERSON"], ["Baffin", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many innings are there in a regulation softball game ?": [["How", "many", "innings", "are", "there", "in", "a", "regulation", "softball", "game", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What would you add to the clay mixture to produce bone china ?": [["What", "would", "you", "add", "to", "the", "clay", "mixture", "to", "produce", "bone", "china", "?"], [["china", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the depth of the Nile river ?": [["What", "is", "the", "depth", "of", "the", "Nile", "river", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the fastest computer ?": [["What", "is", "the", "fastest", "computer", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How do you say 2 in Latin ?": [["How", "do", "you", "say", "2", "in", "Latin", "?"], [["2", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "How"]], "What is the name of the dog on the Cracker Jack box ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "dog", "on", "the", "Cracker", "Jack", "box", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was President Lyndon Johnson 's reform program called ?": [["What", "was", "President", "Lyndon", "Johnson", "'s", "reform", "program", "called", "?"], [["Johnson", "PERSON"], ["Lyndon", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When were camcorders introduced in Malaysia ?": [["When", "were", "camcorders", "introduced", "in", "Malaysia", "?"], [["Malaysia", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What was the first TV set to include a remote control ?": [["What", "was", "the", "first", "TV", "set", "to", "include", "a", "remote", "control", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What century does Captain Video live in ?": [["What", "century", "does", "Captain", "Video", "live", "in", "?"], [["century", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How long does it take the typical hen to lay 19 dozen eggs ?": [["How", "long", "does", "it", "take", "the", "typical", "hen", "to", "lay", "19", "dozen", "eggs", "?"], [["19", "NUMBER"], ["dozen", "NUMBER"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What was Connecticut 's first constitution called ?": [["What", "was", "Connecticut", "'s", "first", "constitution", "called", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Connecticut", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How long is the Columbia River in miles ?": [["How", "long", "is", "the", "Columbia", "River", "in", "miles", "?"], [["Columbia", "LOCATION"], ["River", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "When did the royal wedding of Prince Andrew and Fergie take place ?": [["When", "did", "the", "royal", "wedding", "of", "Prince", "Andrew", "and", "Fergie", "take", "place", "?"], [["Andrew", "PERSON"], ["Fergie", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "Name a movie about the Sioux Indians starring Kevin Costner .": [["Name", "a", "movie", "about", "the", "Sioux", "Indians", "starring", "Kevin", "Costner", "."], [["Kevin", "PERSON"], ["Sioux", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Costner", "PERSON"], ["Indians", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "What gaming devices were dubbed `` Mississippi marbles '' and `` Memphis dominoes '' ?": [["What", "gaming", "devices", "were", "dubbed", "``", "Mississippi", "marbles", "''", "and", "``", "Memphis", "dominoes", "''", "?"], [["Mississippi", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the average life expectancy of a male in Ireland in 1996 ?": [["What", "is", "the", "average", "life", "expectancy", "of", "a", "male", "in", "Ireland", "in", "1996", "?"], [["Ireland", "LOCATION"], ["1996", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is a fear of disease ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "disease", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How loud is thunder ?": [["How", "loud", "is", "thunder", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What Morris West novel deals with Russian bishop who becomes Pope ?": [["What", "Morris", "West", "novel", "deals", "with", "Russian", "bishop", "who", "becomes", "Pope", "?"], [["Pope", "PERSON"], ["Morris", "PERSON"], ["West", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many boys play the game in Winslow Homer 's 1872 painting Snap the Whip ?": [["How", "many", "boys", "play", "the", "game", "in", "Winslow", "Homer", "'s", "1872", "painting", "Snap", "the", "Whip", "?"], [["1872", "DATE"], ["Winslow", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Homer", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What war did the Wanna-Go-Home Riots occur after ?": [["What", "war", "did", "the", "Wanna-Go-Home", "Riots", "occur", "after", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the highest-paying odds on a roulette table ?": [["What", "are", "the", "highest-paying", "odds", "on", "a", "roulette", "table", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What four tastes can a human distinguish ?": [["What", "four", "tastes", "can", "a", "human", "distinguish", "?"], [["four", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many web servers are there ?": [["How", "many", "web", "servers", "are", "there", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What 's the hardest substance in the human body ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "hardest", "substance", "in", "the", "human", "body", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What common plant has a button , cap , cup , gills , and ring ?": [["What", "common", "plant", "has", "a", "button", ",", "cap", ",", "cup", ",", "gills", ",", "and", "ring", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What soft drink would provide me with the biggest intake of caffeine ?": [["What", "soft", "drink", "would", "provide", "me", "with", "the", "biggest", "intake", "of", "caffeine", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the first domesticated bird ?": [["What", "was", "the", "first", "domesticated", "bird", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the Ohio state bird ?": [["What", "is", "the", "Ohio", "state", "bird", "?"], [["Ohio", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many people have been killed in wars , armed conflicts ?": [["How", "many", "people", "have", "been", "killed", "in", "wars", ",", "armed", "conflicts", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What kind of meat is Fray Bentos synonymous with ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "meat", "is", "Fray", "Bentos", "synonymous", "with", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many quarters equal a pound ?": [["How", "many", "quarters", "equal", "a", "pound", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "Name the only extant trilogy of classical Greek plays .": [["Name", "the", "only", "extant", "trilogy", "of", "classical", "Greek", "plays", "."], [], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "How much money does each player get at the beginning of the game in Monopoly ?": [["How", "much", "money", "does", "each", "player", "get", "at", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "game", "in", "Monopoly", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "Which two products use a tiger as their symbol ?": [["Which", "two", "products", "use", "a", "tiger", "as", "their", "symbol", "?"], [["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "What is a fear of drinking ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "drinking", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was another name for East Germany ?": [["What", "was", "another", "name", "for", "East", "Germany", "?"], [["Germany", "LOCATION"], ["East", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 1956 Grace Metalious novel was on the best-seller list for two years ?": [["What", "1956", "Grace", "Metalious", "novel", "was", "on", "the", "best-seller", "list", "for", "two", "years", "?"], [["years", "DURATION"], ["Metalious", "PERSON"], ["two", "DURATION"], ["Grace", "PERSON"], ["1956", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What two vegetables are combined in succotash ?": [["What", "two", "vegetables", "are", "combined", "in", "succotash", "?"], [["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many miles is it from Frankfurt , Germany to Salzburg , Austria ?": [["How", "many", "miles", "is", "it", "from", "Frankfurt", ",", "Germany", "to", "Salzburg", ",", "Austria", "?"], [["Austria", "LOCATION"], ["Salzburg", "LOCATION"], ["Germany", "LOCATION"], ["Frankfurt", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the name for clouds that produce rain ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "for", "clouds", "that", "produce", "rain", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What book did Aaron Hass write ?": [["What", "book", "did", "Aaron", "Hass", "write", "?"], [["Hass", "PERSON"], ["Aaron", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many people in America snore ?": [["How", "many", "people", "in", "America", "snore", "?"], [["America", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What snack food has ridges ?": [["What", "snack", "food", "has", "ridges", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many innings constitute an official baseball game ?": [["How", "many", "innings", "constitute", "an", "official", "baseball", "game", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many miles are there between Tel Aviv , Israel and Memphis , Tennessee ?": [["How", "many", "miles", "are", "there", "between", "Tel", "Aviv", ",", "Israel", "and", "Memphis", ",", "Tennessee", "?"], [["Aviv", "LOCATION"], ["Israel", "LOCATION"], ["Memphis", "LOCATION"], ["Tel", "LOCATION"], ["Tennessee", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many equal angles are there in an isosceles triangle ?": [["How", "many", "equal", "angles", "are", "there", "in", "an", "isosceles", "triangle", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What does 7847+5943 equal ?": [["What", "does", "7847+5943", "equal", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "How old was Sir Edmund Hillary when he climbed Mt . Everest ?": [["How", "old", "was", "Sir", "Edmund", "Hillary", "when", "he", "climbed", "Mt", ".", "Everest", "?"], [["Edmund", "PERSON"], ["Hillary", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many people are there in the world ?": [["How", "many", "people", "are", "there", "in", "the", "world", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What Homerian epic chronicles events toward the end of the Trojan Wars ?": [["What", "Homerian", "epic", "chronicles", "events", "toward", "the", "end", "of", "the", "Trojan", "Wars", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many miles is it from NY to Austria ?": [["How", "many", "miles", "is", "it", "from", "NY", "to", "Austria", "?"], [["Austria", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is Judy Garland 's date of birth ?": [["What", "is", "Judy", "Garland", "'s", "date", "of", "birth", "?"], [["Garland", "PERSON"], ["Judy", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What was the Bridge of San Luis Rey made of ?": [["What", "was", "the", "Bridge", "of", "San", "Luis", "Rey", "made", "of", "?"], [["San", "LOCATION"], ["Luis", "LOCATION"], ["Rey", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was the Battle of Hastings ?": [["When", "was", "the", "Battle", "of", "Hastings", "?"], [["Hastings", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How long does a fly live ?": [["How", "long", "does", "a", "fly", "live", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What fraction of a beaver 's life is spent swimming ?": [["What", "fraction", "of", "a", "beaver", "'s", "life", "is", "spent", "swimming", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many milligrams are in a gram ?": [["How", "many", "milligrams", "are", "in", "a", "gram", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "When was `` the Great Depression '' ?": [["When", "was", "``", "the", "Great", "Depression", "''", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What are the names of all the U.S. Navy aircraft carriers ?": [["What", "are", "the", "names", "of", "all", "the", "U.S.", "Navy", "aircraft", "carriers", "?"], [["Navy", "ORGANIZATION"], ["U.S", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many bones are there in the human hand ?": [["How", "many", "bones", "are", "there", "in", "the", "human", "hand", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What 's destroyed in Genesis 19 : 24 ?": [["What", "'s", "destroyed", "in", "Genesis", "19", ":", "24", "?"], [["19", "NUMBER"], ["24", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What measures did Clinton take to avoid the draft ?": [["What", "measures", "did", "Clinton", "take", "to", "avoid", "the", "draft", "?"], [["Clinton", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does Visine get out ?": [["What", "does", "Visine", "get", "out", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does a polyorchid man have at least three of ?": [["What", "does", "a", "polyorchid", "man", "have", "at", "least", "three", "of", "?"], [["three", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much snow equals an inch of rain ?": [["How", "much", "snow", "equals", "an", "inch", "of", "rain", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "When did the Bounty mutiny take place ?": [["When", "did", "the", "Bounty", "mutiny", "take", "place", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "When was the Congress of Vienna ?": [["When", "was", "the", "Congress", "of", "Vienna", "?"], [["Vienna", "LOCATION"], ["Congress", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is a technique popularly used to detect birth defects ?": [["What", "is", "a", "technique", "popularly", "used", "to", "detect", "birth", "defects", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What movie has made the most money ?": [["What", "movie", "has", "made", "the", "most", "money", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What colors need to be mixed to get the color pink ?": [["What", "colors", "need", "to", "be", "mixed", "to", "get", "the", "color", "pink", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What cigarette is `` a whole new world '' ?": [["What", "cigarette", "is", "``", "a", "whole", "new", "world", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Martin Luther King Jr. 's real birthday ?": [["What", "is", "Martin", "Luther", "King", "Jr.", "'s", "real", "birthday", "?"], [["Luther", "PERSON"], ["Jr", "PERSON"], ["Martin", "PERSON"], ["King", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How much stronger is the new vitreous carbon material invented by the Tokyo Institute of Technology compared with the material made from cellulose ?": [["How", "much", "stronger", "is", "the", "new", "vitreous", "carbon", "material", "invented", "by", "the", "Tokyo", "Institute", "of", "Technology", "compared", "with", "the", "material", "made", "from", "cellulose", "?"], [["Institute", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Tokyo", "ORGANIZATION"], ["of", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Technology", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the chemical formula for napalm ?": [["What", "is", "the", "chemical", "formula", "for", "napalm", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What drug did Sigmund Freud become fascinated with while experimenting with the treatment of neurasthenia ?": [["What", "drug", "did", "Sigmund", "Freud", "become", "fascinated", "with", "while", "experimenting", "with", "the", "treatment", "of", "neurasthenia", "?"], [["Freud", "PERSON"], ["Sigmund", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What articles of clothing are tokens in Monopoly ?": [["What", "articles", "of", "clothing", "are", "tokens", "in", "Monopoly", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How long do hermit crabs live ?": [["How", "long", "do", "hermit", "crabs", "live", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What are the diseases that can be cured by black cumin ?": [["What", "are", "the", "diseases", "that", "can", "be", "cured", "by", "black", "cumin", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the first six words of Dickens 's A Tale of Two Cities ?": [["What", "are", "the", "first", "six", "words", "of", "Dickens", "'s", "A", "Tale", "of", "Two", "Cities", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Dickens", "PERSON"], ["Two", "NUMBER"], ["six", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of sourness ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "sourness", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What format was the major competition of VHS ?": [["What", "format", "was", "the", "major", "competition", "of", "VHS", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What were Christopher Columbus ' three ships ?": [["What", "were", "Christopher", "Columbus", "'", "three", "ships", "?"], [["Columbus", "PERSON"], ["Christopher", "PERSON"], ["three", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Name the vessel used by the Atari Force in the DC comics .": [["Name", "the", "vessel", "used", "by", "the", "Atari", "Force", "in", "the", "DC", "comics", "."], [["Atari", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Force", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "What ill-fated craft was captained by Ernst Lehmann ?": [["What", "ill-fated", "craft", "was", "captained", "by", "Ernst", "Lehmann", "?"], [["Lehmann", "PERSON"], ["Ernst", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What magazine paid $ 5 , 000 for an eight-millimeter film of John F. Kennedy 's assassination ?": [["What", "magazine", "paid", "$", "5", ",", "000", "for", "an", "eight-millimeter", "film", "of", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", "'s", "assassination", "?"], [["5", "MONEY"], ["$", "MONEY"], ["F", "PERSON"], ["Kennedy", "PERSON"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["000", "MONEY"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many Americans fought for the British in the American Revolution ?": [["How", "many", "Americans", "fought", "for", "the", "British", "in", "the", "American", "Revolution", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is a fear of thunder ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "thunder", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What auto race was Wilbur Reed the first to win three times ?": [["What", "auto", "race", "was", "Wilbur", "Reed", "the", "first", "to", "win", "three", "times", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["three", "NUMBER"], ["Wilbur", "PERSON"], ["Reed", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What medium is Stuart Hamblen the first singing cowboy in ?": [["What", "medium", "is", "Stuart", "Hamblen", "the", "first", "singing", "cowboy", "in", "?"], [["Hamblen", "PERSON"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Stuart", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many times a day should you take a prescription marked `` q.i.d . '' ?": [["How", "many", "times", "a", "day", "should", "you", "take", "a", "prescription", "marked", "``", "q.i.d", ".", "''", "?"], [["day", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many inches over six feet is the Venus de Milo ?": [["How", "many", "inches", "over", "six", "feet", "is", "the", "Venus", "de", "Milo", "?"], [["Milo", "PERSON"], ["de", "PERSON"], ["Venus", "PERSON"], ["six", "NUMBER"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What interesting method was used to run the credits in the early Popeye cartoons ?": [["What", "interesting", "method", "was", "used", "to", "run", "the", "credits", "in", "the", "early", "Popeye", "cartoons", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What ship did Lloyd M. Bucher command ?": [["What", "ship", "did", "Lloyd", "M.", "Bucher", "command", "?"], [["Bucher", "PERSON"], ["M", "PERSON"], ["Lloyd", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many people did the United Nations commit to help restore order and distribute humanitarian relief in Somalia in September 1992 ?": [["How", "many", "people", "did", "the", "United", "Nations", "commit", "to", "help", "restore", "order", "and", "distribute", "humanitarian", "relief", "in", "Somalia", "in", "September", "1992", "?"], [["1992", "DATE"], ["United", "ORGANIZATION"], ["September", "DATE"], ["Nations", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Somalia", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What flower did Vincent Van Gogh paint ?": [["What", "flower", "did", "Vincent", "Van", "Gogh", "paint", "?"], [["Van", "PERSON"], ["Vincent", "PERSON"], ["Gogh", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "The Jewish alphabet is known as what ?": [["The", "Jewish", "alphabet", "is", "known", "as", "what", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "The"]], "When did Idaho become a state ?": [["When", "did", "Idaho", "become", "a", "state", "?"], [["Idaho", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What do you call a group of geese ?": [["What", "do", "you", "call", "a", "group", "of", "geese", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Maurizio Pellegrin 's age ?": [["What", "is", "Maurizio", "Pellegrin", "'s", "age", "?"], [["Maurizio", "PERSON"], ["Pellegrin", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many languages does the Pope speak ?": [["How", "many", "languages", "does", "the", "Pope", "speak", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the brand name of a chemical used to control ripening ?": [["What", "is", "the", "brand", "name", "of", "a", "chemical", "used", "to", "control", "ripening", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the different types of plastic ?": [["What", "are", "the", "different", "types", "of", "plastic", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of Sergeant Preston of the Yukon 's lead dog ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "Sergeant", "Preston", "of", "the", "Yukon", "'s", "lead", "dog", "?"], [["Preston", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Garry Kasparov plays what game ?": [["Garry", "Kasparov", "plays", "what", "game", "?"], [["Garry", "PERSON"], ["Kasparov", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Garry"]], "What is the world 's best selling cookie ?": [["What", "is", "the", "world", "'s", "best", "selling", "cookie", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What computer operating system is on the most computers ?": [["What", "computer", "operating", "system", "is", "on", "the", "most", "computers", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What two vessels fought the first sea battle between iron-covered ships ?": [["What", "two", "vessels", "fought", "the", "first", "sea", "battle", "between", "iron-covered", "ships", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What carries sperm up into the pelvic region ?": [["What", "carries", "sperm", "up", "into", "the", "pelvic", "region", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Italy is the largest producer of what ?": [["Italy", "is", "the", "largest", "producer", "of", "what", "?"], [["Italy", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "Italy"]], "How many names are there for Eskimo people ?": [["How", "many", "names", "are", "there", "for", "Eskimo", "people", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "In what movie is the number nine found in the title ?": [["In", "what", "movie", "is", "the", "number", "nine", "found", "in", "the", "title", "?"], [["nine", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "In"]], "What was the eighth day following the Nones in each month of the Roman calendar called ?": [["What", "was", "the", "eighth", "day", "following", "the", "Nones", "in", "each", "month", "of", "the", "Roman", "calendar", "called", "?"], [["eighth", "DATE"], ["month", "SET"], ["day", "DATE"], ["each", "SET"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What race is 1 , 137 miles long ?": [["What", "race", "is", "1", ",", "137", "miles", "long", "?"], [["137", "NUMBER"], ["1", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the term for the side of the mountain that faces the prevailing winds ?": [["What", "is", "the", "term", "for", "the", "side", "of", "the", "mountain", "that", "faces", "the", "prevailing", "winds", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the signs of a country going into a recession ?": [["What", "are", "the", "signs", "of", "a", "country", "going", "into", "a", "recession", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When did Hawaii become a state ?": [["When", "did", "Hawaii", "become", "a", "state", "?"], [["Hawaii", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How much folic acid should a pregnant woman get each day ?": [["How", "much", "folic", "acid", "should", "a", "pregnant", "woman", "get", "each", "day", "?"], [["day", "SET"], ["each", "SET"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "When was Dubai 's first concrete house built ?": [["When", "was", "Dubai", "'s", "first", "concrete", "house", "built", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Dubai", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What sport was the first televised in the U.S. ?": [["What", "sport", "was", "the", "first", "televised", "in", "the", "U.S.", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["U.S", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What field sport did dentist William Beers promote and write a standard book of rules for ?": [["What", "field", "sport", "did", "dentist", "William", "Beers", "promote", "and", "write", "a", "standard", "book", "of", "rules", "for", "?"], [["William", "PERSON"], ["Beers", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What did Walter Huston remove to perform in the movie The Treasure of the Sierra Madre ?": [["What", "did", "Walter", "Huston", "remove", "to", "perform", "in", "the", "movie", "The", "Treasure", "of", "the", "Sierra", "Madre", "?"], [["Walter", "PERSON"], ["Sierra", "LOCATION"], ["Huston", "PERSON"], ["Madre", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What powdered soft drink mix went into space ?": [["What", "powdered", "soft", "drink", "mix", "went", "into", "space", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How fast does the fastest car go ?": [["How", "fast", "does", "the", "fastest", "car", "go", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What color are seven of every 10 houses in the U.S. ?": [["What", "color", "are", "seven", "of", "every", "10", "houses", "in", "the", "U.S.", "?"], [["U.S", "LOCATION"], ["10", "NUMBER"], ["seven", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of odors , body , ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "odors", ",", "body", ",", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was the Brandenburg Gate in Berlin built ?": [["When", "was", "the", "Brandenburg", "Gate", "in", "Berlin", "built", "?"], [["Brandenburg", "LOCATION"], ["Berlin", "LOCATION"], ["Gate", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How many small businesses are there in the United States ?": [["How", "many", "small", "businesses", "are", "there", "in", "the", "United", "States", "?"], [["United", "LOCATION"], ["States", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What does Final Four refer to in the sports world ?": [["What", "does", "Final", "Four", "refer", "to", "in", "the", "sports", "world", "?"], [["Four", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What animals did The Amazing Three masquerade as ?": [["What", "animals", "did", "The", "Amazing", "Three", "masquerade", "as", "?"], [["Three", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the only primate to lack pigment in the palms of its hands ?": [["What", "is", "the", "only", "primate", "to", "lack", "pigment", "in", "the", "palms", "of", "its", "hands", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the name of the Family Circus 's dog ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "Family", "Circus", "'s", "dog", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does a dipsomaniac crave ?": [["What", "does", "a", "dipsomaniac", "crave", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What do you call a Poker hand with five cards of the same suit ?": [["What", "do", "you", "call", "a", "Poker", "hand", "with", "five", "cards", "of", "the", "same", "suit", "?"], [["five", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What amount of money did the Philippine ex-dictator Marcos steal from the treasury ?": [["What", "amount", "of", "money", "did", "the", "Philippine", "ex-dictator", "Marcos", "steal", "from", "the", "treasury", "?"], [["Marcos", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many movies has Drew Barrymore been in ?": [["How", "many", "movies", "has", "Drew", "Barrymore", "been", "in", "?"], [["Barrymore", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What sport can a free-legged pacer compete in ?": [["What", "sport", "can", "a", "free-legged", "pacer", "compete", "in", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of weakness ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "weakness", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the sequel to The Pink Panther ?": [["What", "was", "the", "sequel", "to", "The", "Pink", "Panther", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What killed Bob Marley ?": [["What", "killed", "Bob", "Marley", "?"], [["Bob", "PERSON"], ["Marley", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How big is our galaxy in diameter ?": [["How", "big", "is", "our", "galaxy", "in", "diameter", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What are the stars made of ?": [["What", "are", "the", "stars", "made", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What cooking oil has `` corn goodness '' ?": [["What", "cooking", "oil", "has", "``", "corn", "goodness", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of strong light ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "strong", "light", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What type of exercise burns the most calories ?": [["What", "type", "of", "exercise", "burns", "the", "most", "calories", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Hawaii 's state flower ?": [["What", "is", "Hawaii", "'s", "state", "flower", "?"], [["Hawaii", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What did Mr. Magoo flog on TV for General Electric ?": [["What", "did", "Mr.", "Magoo", "flog", "on", "TV", "for", "General", "Electric", "?"], [["General", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Electric", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Magoo", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was the battle of the Somme fought ?": [["When", "was", "the", "battle", "of", "the", "Somme", "fought", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What was the longest war in U.S. history ?": [["What", "was", "the", "longest", "war", "in", "U.S.", "history", "?"], [["U.S", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What sport is Chris Jogis a top player of ?": [["What", "sport", "is", "Chris", "Jogis", "a", "top", "player", "of", "?"], [["Chris", "PERSON"], ["Jogis", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the fare cost for the round trip between New York and London on Concorde ?": [["What", "is", "the", "fare", "cost", "for", "the", "round", "trip", "between", "New", "York", "and", "London", "on", "Concorde", "?"], [["London", "LOCATION"], ["New", "LOCATION"], ["York", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the speed of the Mississippi River ?": [["What", "is", "the", "speed", "of", "the", "Mississippi", "River", "?"], [["Mississippi", "LOCATION"], ["River", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What did Edward Binney and Howard Smith invent in 1903 ?": [["What", "did", "Edward", "Binney", "and", "Howard", "Smith", "invent", "in", "1903", "?"], [["Smith", "PERSON"], ["Binney", "PERSON"], ["Edward", "PERSON"], ["Howard", "PERSON"], ["1903", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What percent of world 's fresh water is found in Canada ?": [["What", "percent", "of", "world", "'s", "fresh", "water", "is", "found", "in", "Canada", "?"], [["Canada", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "When did communist control end in Hungary ?": [["When", "did", "communist", "control", "end", "in", "Hungary", "?"], [["Hungary", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What ocean liner burned and sank in Hong Kong harbor ?": [["What", "ocean", "liner", "burned", "and", "sank", "in", "Hong", "Kong", "harbor", "?"], [["Hong", "LOCATION"], ["Kong", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When did the `` Star-Spangled Banner '' become the national anthem ?": [["When", "did", "the", "``", "Star-Spangled", "Banner", "''", "become", "the", "national", "anthem", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is the most radioactive food ?": [["What", "is", "the", "most", "radioactive", "food", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the International Lawn Tennis Challenge Trophy usually called ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "International", "Lawn", "Tennis", "Challenge", "Trophy", "usually", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the percentage of children aged two through eleven who watch ` 'The Simpsons ' ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "percentage", "of", "children", "aged", "two", "through", "eleven", "who", "watch", "`", "'The", "Simpsons", "'", "?"], [["two", "NUMBER"], ["eleven", "NUMBER"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many muscles does an oyster have ?": [["How", "many", "muscles", "does", "an", "oyster", "have", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What does it take to be a hero ?": [["What", "does", "it", "take", "to", "be", "a", "hero", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What did Aaron Hass write ?": [["What", "did", "Aaron", "Hass", "write", "?"], [["Hass", "PERSON"], ["Aaron", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Name a technique widely used to detect birth defects ?": [["Name", "a", "technique", "widely", "used", "to", "detect", "birth", "defects", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "How many verses are in the Bible ?": [["How", "many", "verses", "are", "in", "the", "Bible", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How much is Clara Peller being paid by Wendy 's to say `` Where 's the beef '' ?": [["How", "much", "is", "Clara", "Peller", "being", "paid", "by", "Wendy", "'s", "to", "say", "``", "Where", "'s", "the", "beef", "''", "?"], [["Clara", "PERSON"], ["Peller", "PERSON"], ["Wendy", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the life expectancy of a dollar bill ?": [["What", "is", "the", "life", "expectancy", "of", "a", "dollar", "bill", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many varieties of apple are there ?": [["How", "many", "varieties", "of", "apple", "are", "there", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What developed a crack in 1835 while tolling the death of U.S. Chief Justice John Marshall ?": [["What", "developed", "a", "crack", "in", "1835", "while", "tolling", "the", "death", "of", "U.S.", "Chief", "Justice", "John", "Marshall", "?"], [["1835", "DATE"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["Marshall", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What day of the week sees the most fatal car accidents ?": [["What", "day", "of", "the", "week", "sees", "the", "most", "fatal", "car", "accidents", "?"], [["of", "DATE"], ["week", "DATE"], ["day", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many languages are there in the world ?": [["How", "many", "languages", "are", "there", "in", "the", "world", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What were the names of the three ships used by Columbus ?": [["What", "were", "the", "names", "of", "the", "three", "ships", "used", "by", "Columbus", "?"], [["three", "NUMBER"], ["Columbus", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the colorful Korean traditional dress called ?": [["What", "is", "the", "colorful", "Korean", "traditional", "dress", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the 7 Wonders of the World ?": [["What", "are", "the", "7", "Wonders", "of", "the", "World", "?"], [["7", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What golfing accessory was patented by George Grant on December 12": [["What", "golfing", "accessory", "was", "patented", "by", "George", "Grant", "on", "December", "12"], [["12", "DATE"], ["December", "DATE"], ["Grant", "PERSON"], ["George", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When is the site www.questions.com going to open ?": [["When", "is", "the", "site", "www.questions.com", "going", "to", "open", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is a group of turkeys called ?": [["What", "is", "a", "group", "of", "turkeys", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the official animal of Canada ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "official", "animal", "of", "Canada", "?"], [["Canada", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 1895 H.G . Wells novel was written under the title The Chronic Argonauts ?": [["What", "1895", "H.G", ".", "Wells", "novel", "was", "written", "under", "the", "title", "The", "Chronic", "Argonauts", "?"], [["1895", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When does the Bible say the seasons started ?": [["When", "does", "the", "Bible", "say", "the", "seasons", "started", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What Nantucket shipwreck killed more divers exploring it than the 52 people it sank with ?": [["What", "Nantucket", "shipwreck", "killed", "more", "divers", "exploring", "it", "than", "the", "52", "people", "it", "sank", "with", "?"], [["52", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many objects orbit the Earth ?": [["How", "many", "objects", "orbit", "the", "Earth", "?"], [["Earth", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many dogs pull a sled in the Iditarod ?": [["How", "many", "dogs", "pull", "a", "sled", "in", "the", "Iditarod", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the exchange rate for Australian to American money ?": [["What", "is", "the", "exchange", "rate", "for", "Australian", "to", "American", "money", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What 's the shape of a camel 's spine ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "shape", "of", "a", "camel", "'s", "spine", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are `` darning needles '' and `` horse stingers '' better known as ?": [["What", "are", "``", "darning", "needles", "''", "and", "``", "horse", "stingers", "''", "better", "known", "as", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What James Michener book is subtitled Spanish Travels and Reflections ?": [["What", "James", "Michener", "book", "is", "subtitled", "Spanish", "Travels", "and", "Reflections", "?"], [["Michener", "PERSON"], ["James", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is natural gas composed of ?": [["What", "is", "natural", "gas", "composed", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much iron is in your body ?": [["How", "much", "iron", "is", "in", "your", "body", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What currency does Luxembourg use ?": [["What", "currency", "does", "Luxembourg", "use", "?"], [["Luxembourg", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much does the President get paid ?": [["How", "much", "does", "the", "President", "get", "paid", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What song did Patti Page set people dancing to in 1950 ?": [["What", "song", "did", "Patti", "Page", "set", "people", "dancing", "to", "in", "1950", "?"], [["Page", "PERSON"], ["1950", "DATE"], ["Patti", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What percentage of the body is muscle ?": [["What", "percentage", "of", "the", "body", "is", "muscle", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many people die of tuberculosis yearly ?": [["How", "many", "people", "die", "of", "tuberculosis", "yearly", "?"], [["yearly", "SET"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What movie did Steven Spielberg direct in 1975 ?": [["What", "movie", "did", "Steven", "Spielberg", "direct", "in", "1975", "?"], [["Steven", "PERSON"], ["1975", "DATE"], ["Spielberg", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What animal has the best hearing ?": [["What", "animal", "has", "the", "best", "hearing", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is Latin for incompetent ?": [["What", "is", "Latin", "for", "incompetent", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the common name for a Japanese dwarf tree ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "common", "name", "for", "a", "Japanese", "dwarf", "tree", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a language spoken by the Sioux ?": [["What", "is", "a", "language", "spoken", "by", "the", "Sioux", "?"], [["Sioux", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What sign is the best love match for a horoscope sign ?": [["What", "sign", "is", "the", "best", "love", "match", "for", "a", "horoscope", "sign", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the biggest `` thing '' humans have made ?": [["What", "is", "the", "biggest", "``", "thing", "''", "humans", "have", "made", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Shea and Gould had an office in Los Angeles for how long before closing it ?": [["Shea", "and", "Gould", "had", "an", "office", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "for", "how", "long", "before", "closing", "it", "?"], [["Gould", "PERSON"], ["Shea", "PERSON"], ["Angeles", "LOCATION"], ["Los", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "Shea"]], "What is the main language of Sao Paulo , Brazil ?": [["What", "is", "the", "main", "language", "of", "Sao", "Paulo", ",", "Brazil", "?"], [["Brazil", "LOCATION"], ["Sao", "LOCATION"], ["Paulo", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What operating system do IBM-compatible machines use ?": [["What", "operating", "system", "do", "IBM-compatible", "machines", "use", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What `` magic '' does Mandrake employ ?": [["What", "``", "magic", "''", "does", "Mandrake", "employ", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many days does a typical mayfly live ?": [["How", "many", "days", "does", "a", "typical", "mayfly", "live", "?"], [["days", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is Dudley Do-Right 's horse 's name ?": [["What", "is", "Dudley", "Do-Right", "'s", "horse", "'s", "name", "?"], [["Do-Right", "PERSON"], ["Dudley", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How tall is the replica of the Matterhorn at Disneyland ?": [["How", "tall", "is", "the", "replica", "of", "the", "Matterhorn", "at", "Disneyland", "?"], [["Disneyland", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What do bats eat ?": [["What", "do", "bats", "eat", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What series of trials followed World War II ?": [["What", "series", "of", "trials", "followed", "World", "War", "II", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What type of currency is used in Australia ?": [["What", "type", "of", "currency", "is", "used", "in", "Australia", "?"], [["Australia", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What dog was dubbed The Mortgage Lifter ?": [["What", "dog", "was", "dubbed", "The", "Mortgage", "Lifter", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What beer 's name is translated as `` lion brew '' ?": [["What", "beer", "'s", "name", "is", "translated", "as", "``", "lion", "brew", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What stringed weapon fires a bolt ?": [["What", "stringed", "weapon", "fires", "a", "bolt", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many rows of whiskers does a cat have ?": [["How", "many", "rows", "of", "whiskers", "does", "a", "cat", "have", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What six words follow the line : `` From a jack to a king.. . '' ?": [["What", "six", "words", "follow", "the", "line", ":", "``", "From", "a", "jack", "to", "a", "king..", ".", "''", "?"], [["six", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What age followed the Bronze Age ?": [["What", "age", "followed", "the", "Bronze", "Age", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the date of Iraq 's invasion of Kuwait ?": [["What", "was", "the", "date", "of", "Iraq", "'s", "invasion", "of", "Kuwait", "?"], [["Iraq", "LOCATION"], ["Kuwait", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the chemical reactivity of helium ?": [["What", "is", "the", "chemical", "reactivity", "of", "helium", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "Winnie the Pooh is what kind of animal ?": [["Winnie", "the", "Pooh", "is", "what", "kind", "of", "animal", "?"], [["Winnie", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Winnie"]], "How many spears are there on Kenya 's flag ?": [["How", "many", "spears", "are", "there", "on", "Kenya", "'s", "flag", "?"], [["Kenya", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How far out is the universe ?": [["How", "far", "out", "is", "the", "universe", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is President Nixon 's birthdate ?": [["What", "is", "President", "Nixon", "'s", "birthdate", "?"], [["Nixon", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "When are the Oscars Academy Awards in 1999 ?": [["When", "are", "the", "Oscars", "Academy", "Awards", "in", "1999", "?"], [["1999", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How many minutes were there on the original GE College Bowl clock ?": [["How", "many", "minutes", "were", "there", "on", "the", "original", "GE", "College", "Bowl", "clock", "?"], [["minutes", "DURATION"], ["College", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Bowl", "ORGANIZATION"], ["GE", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What was the first satellite to go into space ?": [["What", "was", "the", "first", "satellite", "to", "go", "into", "space", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What year did the United States pass the Copyright law ?": [["What", "year", "did", "the", "United", "States", "pass", "the", "Copyright", "law", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["United", "LOCATION"], ["States", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What kind of tree graces Lebanon 's flag ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "tree", "graces", "Lebanon", "'s", "flag", "?"], [["Lebanon", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How long did Rip Van Winkle sleep ?": [["How", "long", "did", "Rip", "Van", "Winkle", "sleep", "?"], [["Rip", "PERSON"], ["Van", "PERSON"], ["Winkle", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the correct way to mount a roll of toilet paper ?": [["What", "is", "the", "correct", "way", "to", "mount", "a", "roll", "of", "toilet", "paper", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many states did Richard Nixon carry in 1972 ?": [["How", "many", "states", "did", "Richard", "Nixon", "carry", "in", "1972", "?"], [["1972", "DATE"], ["Nixon", "PERSON"], ["Richard", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "Name a film in which Jude Law acted .": [["Name", "a", "film", "in", "which", "Jude", "Law", "acted", "."], [], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "What beer tells us , `` Grab all the gusto you can get . '' ?": [["What", "beer", "tells", "us", ",", "``", "Grab", "all", "the", "gusto", "you", "can", "get", ".", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the Pennsylvania state income tax rate ?": [["What", "is", "the", "Pennsylvania", "state", "income", "tax", "rate", "?"], [["Pennsylvania", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many bones are in the human hand ?": [["How", "many", "bones", "are", "in", "the", "human", "hand", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the state flower of Michigan ?": [["What", "is", "the", "state", "flower", "of", "Michigan", "?"], [["Michigan", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does the Statue of Liberty wear on her feet ?": [["What", "does", "the", "Statue", "of", "Liberty", "wear", "on", "her", "feet", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the smallest thing seen under the most powerful microscope , and how big is it ?": [["What", "is", "the", "smallest", "thing", "seen", "under", "the", "most", "powerful", "microscope", ",", "and", "how", "big", "is", "it", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the date of Mexico 's independence ?": [["What", "is", "the", "date", "of", "Mexico", "'s", "independence", "?"], [["Mexico", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "When is Father 's Day ?": [["When", "is", "Father", "'s", "Day", "?"], [["'s", "DATE"], ["Day", "DATE"], ["Father", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "What is the term for the sum of all genetic material in a given organism ?": [["What", "is", "the", "term", "for", "the", "sum", "of", "all", "genetic", "material", "in", "a", "given", "organism", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many bottles of wine were prisoners in the Bastille allowed per day ?": [["How", "many", "bottles", "of", "wine", "were", "prisoners", "in", "the", "Bastille", "allowed", "per", "day", "?"], [["day", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What do flatfish eat ?": [["What", "do", "flatfish", "eat", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What Nevil Shute novel is about the doomed survivors of a nuclear war ?": [["What", "Nevil", "Shute", "novel", "is", "about", "the", "doomed", "survivors", "of", "a", "nuclear", "war", "?"], [["Shute", "PERSON"], ["Nevil", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What book opens : `` At a certain village in La Mancha , which I shall not name.. . '' ?": [["What", "book", "opens", ":", "``", "At", "a", "certain", "village", "in", "La", "Mancha", ",", "which", "I", "shall", "not", "name..", ".", "''", "?"], [["Mancha", "LOCATION"], ["La", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are all the different kinds of contraceptives ?": [["What", "are", "all", "the", "different", "kinds", "of", "contraceptives", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of cold ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "cold", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What did Englishman John Hawkins begin selling to New World colonists in 1562 ?": [["What", "did", "Englishman", "John", "Hawkins", "begin", "selling", "to", "New", "World", "colonists", "in", "1562", "?"], [["Hawkins", "PERSON"], ["1562", "DATE"], ["John", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What 's the geographic term for the submerged fringe of a continent ?": [["What", "'s", "the", "geographic", "term", "for", "the", "submerged", "fringe", "of", "a", "continent", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Which side should a bowler facing a 37803 split hit the 3-pin on-the left or the right ?": [["Which", "side", "should", "a", "bowler", "facing", "a", "37803", "split", "hit", "the", "3-pin", "on-the", "left", "or", "the", "right", "?"], [["37803", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "What is predicted to topple over between 2010 and 2020 ?": [["What", "is", "predicted", "to", "topple", "over", "between", "2010", "and", "2020", "?"], [["2020", "DATE"], ["2010", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What were hairy bank notes in the fur trade ?": [["What", "were", "hairy", "bank", "notes", "in", "the", "fur", "trade", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What can one see in Reims ?": [["What", "can", "one", "see", "in", "Reims", "?"], [["one", "NUMBER"], ["Reims", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What will a kid eat the middle of , and save the chocolate on the outside for last ?": [["What", "will", "a", "kid", "eat", "the", "middle", "of", ",", "and", "save", "the", "chocolate", "on", "the", "outside", "for", "last", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In Beetle Bailey , can you name Sarge 's dog ?": [["In", "Beetle", "Bailey", ",", "can", "you", "name", "Sarge", "'s", "dog", "?"], [["Beetle", "PERSON"], ["Bailey", "PERSON"], ["Sarge", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "In"]], "What is the federal minimum wage ?": [["What", "is", "the", "federal", "minimum", "wage", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What are cigarettes made of ?": [["What", "are", "cigarettes", "made", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What newspaper serves Salt Lake City ?": [["What", "newspaper", "serves", "Salt", "Lake", "City", "?"], [["Salt", "LOCATION"], ["City", "LOCATION"], ["Lake", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What kind of guitar did Jimi Hendrix play ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "guitar", "did", "Jimi", "Hendrix", "play", "?"], [["Hendrix", "PERSON"], ["Jimi", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the top box office movie in April 1998 ?": [["What", "was", "the", "top", "box", "office", "movie", "in", "April", "1998", "?"], [["April", "DATE"], ["1998", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was a California prayer book to an Old West gambler ?": [["What", "was", "a", "California", "prayer", "book", "to", "an", "Old", "West", "gambler", "?"], [["California", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the electrical output in Madrid , Spain ?": [["What", "is", "the", "electrical", "output", "in", "Madrid", ",", "Spain", "?"], [["Spain", "LOCATION"], ["Madrid", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How big is the Chappellet vineyard ?": [["How", "big", "is", "the", "Chappellet", "vineyard", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "About how many Americans are still unaccounted for from the Vietnam war ?": [["About", "how", "many", "Americans", "are", "still", "unaccounted", "for", "from", "the", "Vietnam", "war", "?"], [["Vietnam", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "About"]], "What is Nero Wolfe 's favorite drink during office hours ?": [["What", "is", "Nero", "Wolfe", "'s", "favorite", "drink", "during", "office", "hours", "?"], [["hours", "DURATION"], ["Wolfe", "PERSON"], ["Nero", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are birds descendents of ?": [["What", "are", "birds", "descendents", "of", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What are the historical trials following World War II called ?": [["What", "are", "the", "historical", "trials", "following", "World", "War", "II", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is a fear of reptiles ?": [["What", "is", "a", "fear", "of", "reptiles", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How big is a quart ?": [["How", "big", "is", "a", "quart", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What fossilizes to form coprolite ?": [["What", "fossilizes", "to", "form", "coprolite", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What animals can live the longest without food ?": [["What", "animals", "can", "live", "the", "longest", "without", "food", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What kind of mammal is a colt ?": [["What", "kind", "of", "mammal", "is", "a", "colt", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In what year was the first patent for the pull-tab opener on cans obtained ?": [["In", "what", "year", "was", "the", "first", "patent", "for", "the", "pull-tab", "opener", "on", "cans", "obtained", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["year", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "When was the USSR dissolved ?": [["When", "was", "the", "USSR", "dissolved", "?"], [["USSR", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "How old is the Italian artist Maurizio Pellegrin ?": [["How", "old", "is", "the", "Italian", "artist", "Maurizio", "Pellegrin", "?"], [["Maurizio", "PERSON"], ["Pellegrin", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many Fig Newtons are there to the pound ?": [["How", "many", "Fig", "Newtons", "are", "there", "to", "the", "pound", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the main ingredient of yogurt ?": [["What", "is", "the", "main", "ingredient", "of", "yogurt", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What sports magazine has the largest circulation ?": [["What", "sports", "magazine", "has", "the", "largest", "circulation", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What game do Steve McQueen and Edward G. Robinson play in The Cincinnati Kid ?": [["What", "game", "do", "Steve", "McQueen", "and", "Edward", "G.", "Robinson", "play", "in", "The", "Cincinnati", "Kid", "?"], [["McQueen", "PERSON"], ["Steve", "PERSON"], ["Cincinnati", "LOCATION"], ["G", "PERSON"], ["Edward", "PERSON"], ["Robinson", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the length of border between the Ukraine and Russia ?": [["What", "is", "the", "length", "of", "border", "between", "the", "Ukraine", "and", "Russia", "?"], [["Russia", "LOCATION"], ["Ukraine", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many hostages were killed in the Entebbe raid ?": [["How", "many", "hostages", "were", "killed", "in", "the", "Entebbe", "raid", "?"], [["Entebbe", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the name of the American literary era that includes 1896 ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "American", "literary", "era", "that", "includes", "1896", "?"], [["1896", "DATE"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many calories are there in a glass of water ?": [["How", "many", "calories", "are", "there", "in", "a", "glass", "of", "water", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is the weakest bone in the body ?": [["What", "is", "the", "weakest", "bone", "in", "the", "body", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Which thrilled taste buds first - Snickers or 3 Musketeers ?": [["Which", "thrilled", "taste", "buds", "first", "-", "Snickers", "or", "3", "Musketeers", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["3", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "When did beethoven die ?": [["When", "did", "beethoven", "die", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What season does a hiemal activity normally take place in ?": [["What", "season", "does", "a", "hiemal", "activity", "normally", "take", "place", "in", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the formula to calculate pi ?": [["What", "is", "the", "formula", "to", "calculate", "pi", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How far is it from Denver to Aspen ?": [["How", "far", "is", "it", "from", "Denver", "to", "Aspen", "?"], [["Aspen", "LOCATION"], ["Denver", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What Mary Tyler Moore Show regular came into the world as Tadeus Wladyslaw Konopka ?": [["What", "Mary", "Tyler", "Moore", "Show", "regular", "came", "into", "the", "world", "as", "Tadeus", "Wladyslaw", "Konopka", "?"], [["Wladyslaw", "PERSON"], ["Mary", "PERSON"], ["Konopka", "PERSON"], ["Moore", "PERSON"], ["Tadeus", "PERSON"], ["Tyler", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What holidays are celebrated in Ireland ?": [["What", "holidays", "are", "celebrated", "in", "Ireland", "?"], [["Ireland", "LOCATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the youngest age a boy or girl can have an orgasm ?": [["What", "is", "the", "youngest", "age", "a", "boy", "or", "girl", "can", "have", "an", "orgasm", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "When was Calypso music invented ?": [["When", "was", "Calypso", "music", "invented", "?"], [], ["NUM", "When"]], "What D.H. Lawrence novel was originally titled Tenderness ?": [["What", "D.H.", "Lawrence", "novel", "was", "originally", "titled", "Tenderness", "?"], [["D.H", "PERSON"], ["Lawrence", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does a philatelist collect ?": [["What", "does", "a", "philatelist", "collect", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What organic fuel do bog-dwellers use a `` slane '' to cut ?": [["What", "organic", "fuel", "do", "bog-dwellers", "use", "a", "``", "slane", "''", "to", "cut", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many freckles does Howdy Doody have on his face ?": [["How", "many", "freckles", "does", "Howdy", "Doody", "have", "on", "his", "face", "?"], [["Doody", "PERSON"], ["Howdy", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "In what medium is Stuart Hamblen considered to be the first singing cowboy ?": [["In", "what", "medium", "is", "Stuart", "Hamblen", "considered", "to", "be", "the", "first", "singing", "cowboy", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Stuart", "PERSON"], ["Hamblen", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "In"]], "What is the longest major league baseball-winning streak ?": [["What", "is", "the", "longest", "major", "league", "baseball-winning", "streak", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What newspaper returned a Pulitzer Prize for the fraudulent story Jimmy 's World ?": [["What", "newspaper", "returned", "a", "Pulitzer", "Prize", "for", "the", "fraudulent", "story", "Jimmy", "'s", "World", "?"], [["Jimmy", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many times a year does the American Gourd Society publish The Gourd ?": [["How", "many", "times", "a", "year", "does", "the", "American", "Gourd", "Society", "publish", "The", "Gourd", "?"], [["a", "DURATION"], ["American", "ORGANIZATION"], ["year", "DURATION"], ["Society", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What was the number of assassinations and attempts to assassinate in the U.S. since 1865 ?": [["What", "was", "the", "number", "of", "assassinations", "and", "attempts", "to", "assassinate", "in", "the", "U.S.", "since", "1865", "?"], [["U.S", "LOCATION"], ["1865", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "How many cubic feet of space does a gallon of water occupy ?": [["How", "many", "cubic", "feet", "of", "space", "does", "a", "gallon", "of", "water", "occupy", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many questions are on this thing ?": [["How", "many", "questions", "are", "on", "this", "thing", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What is a 2-sided object called ?": [["What", "is", "a", "2-sided", "object", "called", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What month , date , and year did Charles I die ?": [["What", "month", ",", "date", ",", "and", "year", "did", "Charles", "I", "die", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["month", "DURATION"], ["Charles", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What 's played at Wembley Stadium , London , every May ?": [["What", "'s", "played", "at", "Wembley", "Stadium", ",", "London", ",", "every", "May", "?"], [["Wembley", "LOCATION"], ["Stadium", "LOCATION"], ["London", "LOCATION"], ["May", "SET"], ["every", "SET"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "When was Florida admitted into the Union ?": [["When", "was", "Florida", "admitted", "into", "the", "Union", "?"], [["Florida", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "When"]], "On what day were John F and Jackie Kennedy married ?": [["On", "what", "day", "were", "John", "F", "and", "Jackie", "Kennedy", "married", "?"], [["Jackie", "PERSON"], ["F", "PERSON"], ["day", "DURATION"], ["John", "PERSON"], ["Kennedy", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "On"]], "What time of day did Emperor Hirohito die ?": [["What", "time", "of", "day", "did", "Emperor", "Hirohito", "die", "?"], [["day", "DURATION"], ["Hirohito", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "What"]], "What brand of jeans did Calvin Klein admit in a 1984 interview he felt more comfortable wearing ?": [["What", "brand", "of", "jeans", "did", "Calvin", "Klein", "admit", "in", "a", "1984", "interview", "he", "felt", "more", "comfortable", "wearing", "?"], [["Calvin", "PERSON"], ["1984", "DATE"], ["Klein", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the life span of the average monkey ?": [["What", "is", "the", "life", "span", "of", "the", "average", "monkey", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What blood sport features a movement called a veronica ?": [["What", "blood", "sport", "features", "a", "movement", "called", "a", "veronica", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What therapy attempts to elicit the `` primal scream '' ?": [["What", "therapy", "attempts", "to", "elicit", "the", "``", "primal", "scream", "''", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many people have died of tuberculosis ?": [["How", "many", "people", "have", "died", "of", "tuberculosis", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What were the first frozen foods ?": [["What", "were", "the", "first", "frozen", "foods", "?"], [["first", "ORDINAL"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What is the chance of conceiving quadruplets ?": [["What", "is", "the", "chance", "of", "conceiving", "quadruplets", "?"], [], ["NUM", "What"]], "What is the name of the song that Dracula plays on the organ ?": [["What", "is", "the", "name", "of", "the", "song", "that", "Dracula", "plays", "on", "the", "organ", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What does a spermologer collect ?": [["What", "does", "a", "spermologer", "collect", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What car was driven in the 199 release of `` Smokey and the Bandit '' ?": [["What", "car", "was", "driven", "in", "the", "199", "release", "of", "``", "Smokey", "and", "the", "Bandit", "''", "?"], [["199", "NUMBER"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "In what year did Joe DiMaggio compile his 56-game hitting streak ?": [["In", "what", "year", "did", "Joe", "DiMaggio", "compile", "his", "56-game", "hitting", "streak", "?"], [["Joe", "PERSON"], ["DiMaggio", "PERSON"], ["year", "DURATION"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "Which infectious disease kills the most people worldwide ?": [["Which", "infectious", "disease", "kills", "the", "most", "people", "worldwide", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "Which"]], "What is a synonym for aspartame ?": [["What", "is", "a", "synonym", "for", "aspartame", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How much would it cost to purchase a 2-foot-square party tent , with sides , ?": [["How", "much", "would", "it", "cost", "to", "purchase", "a", "2-foot-square", "party", "tent", ",", "with", "sides", ",", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "How many votes in Congress dissented from the 1941 declaration of war with Japan ?": [["How", "many", "votes", "in", "Congress", "dissented", "from", "the", "1941", "declaration", "of", "war", "with", "Japan", "?"], [["1941", "DATE"], ["Congress", "ORGANIZATION"], ["Japan", "LOCATION"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "In what year did Hitler gain power of Germany ?": [["In", "what", "year", "did", "Hitler", "gain", "power", "of", "Germany", "?"], [["year", "DURATION"], ["Germany", "LOCATION"], ["Hitler", "PERSON"]], ["NUM", "In"]], "How many years ago did the ship Titanic sink ?": [["How", "many", "years", "ago", "did", "the", "ship", "Titanic", "sink", "?"], [["years", "DATE"], ["ago", "DATE"]], ["NUM", "How"]], "What are the rites accompanying the circumcision of a newly born-child in Judaism called ?": [["What", "are", "the", "rites", "accompanying", "the", "circumcision", "of", "a", "newly", "born-child", "in", "Judaism", "called", "?"], [["Judaism", "ORGANIZATION"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "How many pounds are there in a stone ?": [["How", "many", "pounds", "are", "there", "in", "a", "stone", "?"], [], ["NUM", "How"]], "What alloy do copper and tin form ?": [["What", "alloy", "do", "copper", "and", "tin", "form", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of the `` Little Rascals '' dog ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "the", "``", "Little", "Rascals", "''", "dog", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What was the name of the horse that fell on Queen Elizabeth , Prince Albert 's wife ?": [["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "the", "horse", "that", "fell", "on", "Queen", "Elizabeth", ",", "Prince", "Albert", "'s", "wife", "?"], [["Elizabeth", "PERSON"], ["Albert", "PERSON"], ["Prince", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "What"]], "What net game sees its women 's world amateur champions receive the Uber Cup ?": [["What", "net", "game", "sees", "its", "women", "'s", "world", "amateur", "champions", "receive", "the", "Uber", "Cup", "?"], [], ["ENTY", "What"]], "Name the story by Chris Van Allsburg in the which a boy tries to become a great sailor ?": [["Name", "the", "story", "by", "Chris", "Van", "Allsburg", "in", "the", "which", "a", "boy", "tries", "to", "become", "a", "great", "sailor", "?"], [["Van", "PERSON"], ["Chris", "PERSON"], ["Allsburg", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "Name the French historical period during the reign of Napoleon III .": [["Name", "the", "French", "historical", "period", "during", "the", "reign", "of", "Napoleon", "III", "."], [["III", "PERSON"], ["Napoleon", "PERSON"]], ["ENTY", "Name"]], "What daily newspaper will `` help you see clearer across the USA '' ?": [["What", "daily", "newspaper", "will", "``", "help", "you", "see", "clearer", "across", "the", "USA", "''", "?"], [["USA", "LO